{
    "subject": "Abel_Gance",
    "predicate": "produced",
    "object": "J'accuse!__1938_film_",
    "human_readable": "Abel Gance produced the film J'accuse! (1938).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8964362144470215,
            "question": "Who produced the film J'accuse!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7599543333053589,
            "question": "What year was the film J'accuse! released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7010834217071533,
            "question": "Is Abel Gance known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6950716972351074,
            "question": "What makes J'accuse! a significant film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6191450953483582,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6169033050537109,
            "question": "What was the historical context surrounding the release of J'accuse!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5758678913116455,
            "question": "What genre is the film J'accuse!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5274366140365601,
            "question": "How did J'accuse! impact cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4348081350326538,
            "question": "Can you name another film by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3921963572502136,
            "question": "What are some common themes in Abel Gance's films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abel Gance produced the film J'accuse! (1938).",
            "html": "yago_4160_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another film by Abel Gance?",
            "html": "yago_4160_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did J'accuse! impact cinema?",
            "html": "yago_4160_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film J'accuse!",
            "html": "yago_4160_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4160_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4160_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4160_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4160_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4160_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4160_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4160_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4160_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4160_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4160_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Abel Gance produced the film J'accuse! (1938). The texts mention that Abel Gance released a version of J'Accuse in 1938, and it is stated as a fact about him."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Abel Gance produced the film \"J'accuse!\" in 1938. Specifically, the document at `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_4160/re-ranker-msmarco/107.txt` states: \"Released in 1938, Abel Gance\u2019s J\u2019Accuse isn\u2019t so much a remake of his 1919 WWI epic of the same name as an impassioned plea for mercy, and a ceasefire, on the eve of global catastrophe.\" This confirms that Abel Gance was indeed involved in producing \"J'accuse!\" in 1938."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}